

Kashif Abdul Ghafoor

Senior Consultant –SuccessFactors kashifabdulghafoor@gmail.com 0092-336-9773458 Karachi, Sindh, Pakistan.

PERSONAL DETAILS

Date of Birth 20th February 1983

Place of Birth Karachi

Gender Male

Nationality Pakistani

Civil status Married

Linked in linkedin.com/in/kash

b06704127

KEY SKILLS

Leadership.

Problem Solving.

Conversation with clients.

Meets client's expectation.

Focused on Roles & Responsibility.

Risk Management.

Change Management.

Project Management.

Activate Methodology.

SKILLS

Strategic Thinking.

Effective Communication.

Adaptability.

Strong Listening and Questioning.

Profile

08 Year Experience in SAP World, my role as a **Senior Consultant** of SAP SuccessFactors looking into SF modules, certified in (**Performance & Goals, Employee Central, Recruiting Management & Marketing**). Previously I looked after as **Key Account Manager** of SAP - Sales, the experience encompassing a wide range of a skill set roles and most importantly Project Management with Activate Methodology.

Objective.

Looking for a challenging position in a vibrant organization, where I can explore new experience in addition to long-term career opportunities. This will enable me to maximize my abilities in SAP SF Consulting, Marketing & Sales Management and make an immediate contribution as part of a professional team.

Experience.

Senior Consultant - SAP SuccessFactors.

Siemens Pakistan Eng. co. Ltd. 2018 - present

- Experience with analysis, design, development, customization, support, Testing, and implementation of software application.
- Proficient in analyzing and translating business requirements to functional / technical requirement.
- Experience in leading and managing teams, handled multiple roles Team Lead, Senior Consultant, Business Analyst.
- Good Communication Skills, Interpersonal skills, self-motivated, quick learner and a team player.
- Possess project management skills, good communication, business process analysis, consulting, design and documentation skills.

Key Account Manager – Enterprise Business Solution (SAP Sales)

Siemens Pakistan Eng. Co. Ltd. 2016 - 2018

A proven record of account management working on various business development positions for over 3 years focusing target achievement, business growth and customer conformance. Ability to seek market opportunities to break deals in high motivation and spirits by optimizing solution, building customer's confidence while at the same time keeping up with company's and product's positioning to counter market pressures. Developing markets by organizing various forums & platforms creating a healthy environment to position both generic and industry specific solutions alike.

I consent to the processing of my personal data for the purpose of recruitment for the position to which I am applying.

Projects (SuccessFactors)

Current Project.

Shan Foods. OGDCL.

Completed Projects.

Tapal Tea Ltd. Continental Biscuits. Fauji Foods.

Projects (Key Account Mgr.)

Dynea.

Imtiaz Provision Store.

ICI Pakistan.

Pakistan State Oil.

Pakistan Petroleum.

Pak Arab Refinery.

PharmEvo.

Indus Motors.

Engro Corp.

LANGUAGES

English.

Urdu.

ACTIVITIES AND INTERESTS

Playing Cricket & Snooker.

Account Executive – Information Technology Solution

Siemens Pakistan Eng. Co. Ltd. 2015 - 2016

Responsible for market analysis, lead production & lead qualification. Successfully developed technical tools for demand maturity which included technical documentation, preliminary system analysis reports, solution presentations, compliance collaterals, case studies, and success stories. Developed Expression of Interests (EOI) and Request for Proposal (RFP) documents primarily for public sector and listed companies. Developed good working practices with technical and commercial teams.

Other Experience

Head of Performance & Reporting - Travel Admin Human Resource Department.

SIEMENS PAKISTAN ENG. CO. LTD. 2012 – 2015

- Deploy Travel strategy of businesses
- Define concrete local travel actions for Country to achieve strategy and implement
- Cooperate with communication responsible
- Provide content for communication regarding Travel matters
- Provide input on requirements for local Travel IT systems
- Implement IT / information systems (in cooperation with CIT)
- Analyze KPI / data for respective area of responsibility

Industrial Relation Department - Admin officer

SIEMENS PAKISTAN ENG. CO. LTD. 2012 - 2012

- Handling the record of Contract Employees
- Final Settlement of the Contract employees
- Keeping the record of contract employees Over Time.

SAP SuccessFactors Certificates

- Performance & Goals Management
- Employee Central.
- Recruiting Management
- Recruiting Marketing.

Education

BACHELOR'S IN COMMERCE - 2007

KARACHI UNIVERSITY, SINDH, PAKISTAN.

Diploma / Software Engineering.

e-ACCP certification

APTECH COMPUTER EDUCATION.

2001-2005

I consent to the processing of my personal data for the purpose of recruitment for the position to which I am applying.